coming from South Africa we have no
medical yeah travel insurance is of
vital importance our purpose of coming
to Canada was because of our family and
we found now that Charles is retired we
will make the move and live here and we
love it but it is a cultural shock
Calgary is a very cold place but you
adjust we've been with men You love
three and a half years I've had two
incidents unfortunately in 2018 I had a
gallbladder problem and gallstones and
unfortunately last year I saw an upper
Thalamus and he said I had a hole in the
retina with my new life it was extremely
easy we were treated with the utmost
respect the first incident was 48 000
and the second incident was nine
thousand and we were not left out of
pocket at all it would have really been
a catastrophic Financial impact on
ourselves as individuals traveling and
likewise on our family that we are
visiting we would love to grow old with
our family and we will recommend man you
laugh as a travel insurance to any
friends of ours our asset in life is our
health and that's why we have gone
through Manulife for our peace of mind
[Music]